	questionList = questionList.concat([
	
	//Conditional  5
	{question:"The boy would eat.", answers:["El niño comería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El niño comería.", answers:["The boy would eat.", "The child would eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be an apple.", answers:["Sería una manzana."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería una manzana.", answers:["It would be an apple."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Sería una mujer.", answers:["It would be a woman.","She would be a woman.","I would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be a woman.", answers:["Sería una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ella sería una mujer.", answers:["She would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"She would be a woman.", answers:["Sería una mujer.", "Ella sería una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted sería una mujer.", answers:["You would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú serías una mujer.", answers:["You would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Serías una mujer.", answers:["You would be a woman."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would be a woman.", answers:["Usted sería una mujer.", "Tú serías una mujer.", "Serías una mujer."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It would be a girl.", answers:["Sería una niña."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It would be a child.", answers:["Sería una niña.", "Sería un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Usted sería un hombre.", answers:["You would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú serías un hombre.", answers:["You would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Serías un hombre.", answers:["You would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would be a man.", answers:["Usted sería un hombre.", "Tú serías un hombre.", "Serías un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"It would be a boy.", answers:["Sería un niño."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería un niño.", answers:["It would be a boy.", "He would be a boy.","I would be a boy.","It would be a child.","He would be a child.","I would be a child."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be a man.", answers:["Sería un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería un hombre.", answers:["He would be a man.", "It would be a man.","I would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Él sería un hombre.", answers:["He would be a man."], language:"English"},
	{question:"He would be a man.", answers:["Sería un hombre.", "Él sería un hombre."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"El hombre comería.", answers:["The man would eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"The man would eat.", answers:["El hombre comería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú beberías agua.", answers:["You would drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would drink water.", answers:["Tú beberías agua.", "Beberías agua.", "Usted bebería agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo comería.", answers:["I would eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I would eat.", answers:["Comería.","Yo comería."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Un niño bebería.", answers:["A boy would drink.","A child would drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"A boy would drink.", answers:["Un niño bebería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Yo bebería.", answers:["I would drink."], language:"English"},
	{question:"I would drink.", answers:["Yo bebería.", "Bebería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Tú comerías.", answers:["You would eat."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would eat.", answers:["Tú comerías.", "Comerías.", "Usted comería."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería pan.", answers:["It would be bread."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be bread.", answers:["Sería pan."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Sería agua.", answers:["It would be water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"It would be water.", answers:["Sería agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You would be men.", answers:["Ustedes serían hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes serían hombres.", answers:["You would be men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Seríamos hombres.", answers:["We would be men."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We would be men.", answers:["Seríamos hombres.", "Nosotros seríamos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Seríamos mujeres.", answers:["We would be women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We would be women.", answers:["Nosotras seríamos mujeres.", "Seríamos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotras beberíamos leche.", answers:["We would drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros beberíamos leche.", answers:["We would drink milk."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We would drink milk.", answers:["Beberíamos leche.", "Nosotros beberíamos leche.", "Nosotras beberíamos leche."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras beberíamos agua.", answers:["We would drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotros beberíamos agua.", answers:["We would drink water."], language:"English"},
	{question:"We would drink water.", answers:["Beberíamos agua.", "Nosotros beberíamos agua.", "Nosotras beberíamos agua."], language:"English"},
	{question:"You would be women.", answers:["Ustedes serían mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ustedes serían mujeres.", answers:["You would be women."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Nosotras seríamos mujeres.", answers:["We would be women."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We would be women.", answers:["Nosotras seríamos mujeres.","Seríamos mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas serían mujeres.", answers:["They would be women."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They would be women.", answers:["Ellas serían mujeres.","Serían mujeres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"You would drink water.", answers:["Tú beberías agua.", "Beberías agua.", "Usted bebería agua.", "Ustedes beberían agua."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ustedes beberían agua.", answers:["You would drink water."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Ellos serían hombres.", answers:["They would be men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They would be men.", answers:["Ellos serían hombres.", "Serían hombres."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You would drink milk.", answers:["Tú beberías leche.","Beberías leche.","Usted bebería leche.","Ustedes beberían leche."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"Nosotros seríamos hombres.", answers:["We would be men."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We would be men.", answers:["Nosotros seríamos hombres.","Seríamos hombres."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"They would drink.", answers:["Beberían.","Ellos beberían.","Ellas beberían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos beberían.", answers:["They would drink."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Las niñas beberían agua.", answers:["The girls would drink water.","The children would drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls would drink water.", answers:["Las niñas beberían agua."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Los niños beberían agua.", answers:["The boys would drink water.","The children would drink water."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boys would drink water.", answers:["Los niños beberían agua."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Tú escribirías un libro.", answers:["You would write a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You would write a book.", answers:["Tú escribirías un libro.","Escribirías un libro.","Usted escribiría un libro.","Ustedes escribirían un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Usted escribiría un libro.", answers:["You would write a book."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Yo escribiría una carta.", answers:["I would write a letter."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"I would write a letter.", answers:["Yo escribiría una carta.","Escribiría una carta."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Nosotros escribiríamos un libro.", answers:["We would write a book."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"We would write a book.", answers:["Nosotros escribiríamos un libro.","Nosotras escribiríamos un libro.","Escribiríamos un libro."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Ellas beberían vino.", answers:["They would drink wine."], language:"English"},		
	{question:"They would drink wine.", answers:["Ellas beberían vino.","Ellos beberían vino.","Beberían vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"I would drink wine.", answers:["Yo bebería vino.","Bebería vino."], language:"Spanish"},		
	{question:"Yo bebería vino.", answers:["I would drink wine."], language:"English"},
	{question:"Tú leerías el libro.", answers:["You would read the book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"You would read the book.", answers:["Tú leerías el libro.","Leerías el libro.","Usted leería el libro.","Ustedes leerían el libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Las niñas escribirían.", answers:["The girls would write.","The children would write."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The girls would write.", answers:["Las niñas escribirían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ella sería una persona.", answers:["She would be a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"She would be a person.", answers:["Ella sería una persona.","Sería una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo leería.", answers:["I would read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I would read.", answers:["Yo leería.","Leería."], language:"English"},
	{question:"El niño leería.", answers:["The boy would read.","The child would read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"The boy would read.", answers:["El niño leería."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Él sería una persona.", answers:["He would be a person."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"He would be a person.", answers:["Él sería una persona.","Sería una persona."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotros leeríamos un diario.", answers:["We would read a newspaper."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We would read a newspaper.", answers:["Nosotros leeríamos un diario.","Nosotras leeríamos un diario.","Leeríamos un diario."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellas leerían.", answers:["They would read."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They would read.", answers:["Ellas leerían.","Ellos leerían.","Leerían."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos leerían un libro.", answers:["They would read a book."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They would read a book.", answers:["Ellas leerían un libro.","Ellos leerían un libro.","Leerían un libro."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Nosotras comeríamos arroz.", answers:["We would eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"Nosotros comeríamos arroz.", answers:["We would eat rice."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"We would eat rice.", answers:["Nosotras comeríamos arroz.","Nosotros comeríamos arroz.","Comeríamos arroz."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Yo cocinaría pescado.", answers:["I would cook fish."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I would cook fish.", answers:["Yo cocinaría pescado.","Cocinaría pescado."], language:"Spanish"},	
	{question:"Ellos no comerían nada.", answers:["They would not eat anything.","They wouldn't eat anything."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"They would not eat anything.", answers:["Ellos no comerían nada.","Ellas no comerían nada.","No comerían nada."], language:"Spanish"},
	{question:"No cocinaría.", answers:["I would not cook.","I wouldn't cook."], language:"English"},	
	{question:"I would not cook.", answers:["Yo no cocinaría.","No cocinaría."], language:"Spanish"}
	
	]);
